export const quiz = [
	{
		id: 1,
		type: "radio",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4"],
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		type: "checkbox",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4", "sample answer2"],
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		type: "radio",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4"],
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		type: "checkbox",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4", "sample answer2"],
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		type: "radio",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4"],
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		type: "checkbox",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4", "sample answer2"],
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		type: "radio",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4"],
	},
	{
		id: 8,
		type: "checkbox",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4", "sample answer2"],
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		type: "radio",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4"],
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		type: "checkbox",
		question: "Sample Question",
		options: [
			"sample answer1",
			"sample answer2",
			"sample answer3",
			"sample answer4",
		],
		correct_answer: ["sample answer4", "sample answer2"],
	},
];
